http://www.srdinodia.com/privacy-policy

1
2
3
4
With respect to information available from this web page, neither the S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP nor any of its employees make any warranty, express or implied, including the warranty of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, or assume any liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such information.
You acknowledge and agree that all proprietary rights in the information received shall remain the property of S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP Reproduction, redistribution and transmission of any information contained in the web site is strictly prohibited. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP shall not be liable for any claims or losses of any nature, arising indirectly or directly from use of the data or material on this site or unauthorized access to this site or otherwise howsoever arising (except to the extent required by law).
Access to this web site is confirmation that you have understood and accepted these terms.
THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE TO YOU, THE USER. PLEASE READ THIS STATEMENT EACH TIME YOU VISIT THE SITE SO THAT YOU WILL BE FULLY INFORMED OF THE PRIVACY POLICIES AND PROCEDURES OF S.R. DINODIA & CO.LLP
The purpose of this privacy statement is to inform you, the User of this Site, of the procedures and practices utilized by S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP to keep your personal information private once you access this Site. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP believes that your privacy is very important. BY ACCESSING THIS SITE, YOU, THE USER, ARE GIVING YOUR CONSENT AND APPROVAL TO THE PRIVACY PRACTICES AND PROCEDURES OF S.R. DINODIA & CO.LLP
S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP will not knowingly disclose information collected about each User to parties not affiliated with S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP unless required to do so by law. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP does not market to children or knowingly gather information from children for marketing purposes.
Our privacy statement only addresses the use and disclosure of information that S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP may collect from you. However, you should be aware that persons not associated or affiliated with S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP may engage in unauthorized practices with the purpose of obtaining your personal information. Although S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP discourages this type of activity, we cannot guarantee that it will not occur. The Internet can take on a life of its own and therefore, S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP cannot guarantee against inadvertent or unknowing disclosures of information about you, the User, to others. To the extent permitted by law, S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP disclaims all liability for any inadvertent disclosures.
For the convenience of our Alumni, the S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP Site contains a Form. In order to use this Form, the alumni are required to input certain personal information, including, his or her name, address, business and home telephone number, and email address. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP may use this information to contact the Alumni and also for marketing and promotional purposes. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP does not sell, rent or otherwise disseminate this information to non-affiliated entities.
By accessing this Site, you are giving your consent and approval to our privacy policies. This Privacy statement is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions of This Site as though set forth in full. S.R. Dinodia & Co.LLP, All Rights Reserved – 2013.
Pages
About Us
History
Our Team
Mr. Pradeep Dinodia
Mr. Sandeep Dinodia
Ms. Pallavi Dinodia Gupta
Mr. R.P. Mahajan
Tax Review (Due Diligence)
Transaction Evaluation (Due Diligence)
SRD Corporate Profile 2014
Union Budget 2019
Union Budget 2020
Indian Union Budget, 2020 : Highlights of amendments made in Finance Bill, 2020 as passed in Lok Sabha
